Today, the poor girl is in a bad mood even on her birthday.  What happened was that
we were going to our
friend's birthday party.  Got
ready and shady quickly.  Please do let me know in the comments how this dress looks on me.  The
first thing I ate as soon as I left the house was cake.
Wished the birthday girl as soon as I reached the party hall.  And
brother, wherever we girls go, we want to take photos
[music] first of all.  Then came the turn of the most
special moment.  Everyone sang Happy Birthday together.
Cake cut and everyone celebrated their birthday.
But the real party starts now.  Some
ordered pasta and some ordered noodles.  I
also ordered my all time favourite
strawberry shake.  But what happened after this was
not expected at all.  Brother,
I forgot the birthday girl's birthday gift at home.
What could be worse than this, but
somehow I convinced him and brought him home.  I
gave him this cute lap.